Victor David Software Developer

• Lagos, Nigeria

■ vad.inc8@gmail.com

+234 9072045997

★ https://vaad.netlify.app/



PROFILE

I'm a professional task solving Software Developer from Nigeria. I deliver quality and amazing solutions, with high and proficient skills required.

I'm well versed in team collaboration to formulate and conceptualize corporate web presence. Specialty embracing challenging projects requiring detailed coding changes, search engine-related considerations and security. Integrates knowledge of visual arts to develop functional, appealing, custom-made web products and services.

Building & Designing Software Applications with great user experience is also my expertise.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern, Tecklink

Apr 2022 – present Tbilisi, Georgia

- » Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface
- » Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.

Software Engineer, DSC

» Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.

Apr 2019 – Feb 2021 Ekiti, Nigeria

Web developer Intern, SQI ICT

» Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with Html,JavaScript,JAX and JSON Coding.

Sep 2017 – Jan 2019 Oyo, Nigeria

- »Built some great projects like Banking Applications, PWA Chat Applications, Management System for Schools and Churches using Web technologieslike Php, AJAX, MySQL
- » Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface

Victor David 1/2

SKILLS

Frameworks/libraries:

Vue-CLI, Laravel, NodeJs, JQuery, Vuetify, Firebase.

Programming Languages:

JavaScript, Typescript, Python, C++, Java.

Data Science:

Python (Data Aggregation, Data Manipulation, Data Visualization).

Infrastructure/Databases:

Php, SQL, PostgreSQL, Mongo dB, Firestore

Automation / Tooling:

Git, Docker, Kubernetes. , Azure, Gitlab-ci, Circle-ci.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering (B.Eng), Federal University Oye-Ekiti 2019 – 2023

Ekiti, Nigeria

Certificate degree in software development, SQI ICT 2019 – 2021

Oyo, Nigeria

Certificate degree in ICT, SQI ICT 2019

Oyo, Nigeria

High School (FEGO) 2011 – 2017

Oyo, Nigeria

PROJECTS

FuoyeMarket ☑

The mightgain 🛮

Speedyfame 2

Github 🛭

CONTACT

LinkedIn 🗗

Github 2

WhatsApp □

Twitter 🛮

INTERESTS

Coding, Music, Football, Tech research

Victor David 2 / 2